Simon Zirui Guo | 郭子睿

Maker, Hacker, Innovator

I'm a 16-year-old student currently looking for a summer internship for August 2017. I am passionate about Internet of Things, robo cs, and innova on. I have created many hackathon projects and side projects that focus on solving real-life issues via hardware and so ware hacks.

Contact Information

- +1 647 972 1505
- simonguo.tech
- simonguozirui
- simonguozirui
- Toronto, ON, Canada



EXPERIENCE

hack.init()

Co-Founder & Director (2017.2 - now)

Founding and Directing China's largest youth hackathon that brings together 300 brightest minds of next generation's stars of Chinese high-tech industry and break the age barrier currently imposed in 24 hours.

The Knowledge Society

Innovator (2017.2 - now)

Discuss with industry leaders and like-minded youths on the future of cutting-edge technologies, develop innovative mindset, and create innovative solutions that target real-life problems.

The Toronto Hacker Club

.....

Event Coordinator (2016.12 - now)

Promote computer science education across the GTA through tech-related workshops and hackathons. My role consists: website building, corperate relationship, event planning, create event schedule, and mediate workshops.

University of Toronto Robotics Association

Member of the RoboSoccer & SumoBot Team (2016.9 - now)

RoboSoccer: Create 4 humanoid robots to participate in RoboCup Soccer (humanoid kid size category). Part of the control (electrical and mechanical design) system team.

Sumo: Attend weekly workshops on mechanical, electrical, and embedded system of robot design. Create a sumo robot individually and compete in the annual sumo competition.



.....

EDUCATION

Upper Canada College

International Baccalaureate & Ontario Secondary School Diploma (2015.9 - now)

Robotics Club, Co-founder of Engineering Society, Hackathon Coordinator of the Digital Media and Computer Science Club, Science Club, World Affairs Conference, Norval Labs, Debate Club, Senior Wind Ensemble, Debate Club, Cross Country Running Team, Peer Tutoring, Rowing Team

Various Institutions

Summer Programs (2015.7 - now)

University of Toronto Da Vinci Engineering Enrichment Program (DEEP) 2016 Canadian Mathematical Society Math Camp (Invitational) 2016

John Hopkins University Center for Talented Youth (CTY) 2015: Mathematical Logic



Please visit my website (simonguo.tech) for my protofolio and awards.



Circuitry	Web Dev	 Design Thinking	
CAD	HTML 5	Project Managment	
ArduinoC	CSS 3	 Java	
Python 2 & 3	JavaScript	Data Analysis	